The power of darkness that's flowing inside my body...
传遍我全身的暗黑魔力  真是令人怀念的感觉
Liselotte Wreckmeister...
莉泽萝忒·薇露库麦丝塔
Isn't that good?
太好了啊
Yes, it is.
好吧
Let me grant you... your wish.
你的愿望  就由我来实现
Yuka!
结花
Kakeru!
驱
Never!
不对
A precognition?
未来视吗？
You little brat!
雕虫小技
Become your soul
化为魂魄  与所爱之人永远游荡在世间吧
I won't let you have any more power!
我不会再让你得到「碎片」了
Superbia!
斯佩尔比亚
You must not kill him.
不能杀
How foolish...
愚蠢至极  事到如今还无法接受么
Liselotte...
莉泽萝忒
Wanna kill me?
要斩吗
Did you forget that I'm immortal?
你不会忘了我是不死之躯吧？
I just remembered.
我现在明白了
Since you don't possess enough fragments,
现在「碎片」已经不足  能实现你愿望的…
is my right eye.
只有我这右眼
That's right.
没错
That's why,
那么能救结花  救大家和世界的方法只有一个
Don't tell me...
难道说…
I have to die!
只要我死就行了
Kakeru-kun!
驱君
Kukuri-neesan...
菊理姐姐
Yuka...
结花
What are you reading?
你在看什么？
Is it interesting?
好看吗？
The ending...
结局
I like the ending.
我喜欢故事的结局
"And then the two of them lived happily ever after."
「从那以后两个人便在一起  过上了幸福的生活」
I like it too.
我也喜欢
Kakeru-kun...
驱君…
You're gloomy!
阴暗
And creepy!
恶心
Stop it.
别去啊
What's with that girl?
什么啊  那家伙
She makes me mad.
让人火大
Let's go home.
回去吧
Yuka-chan?
结花？
What happened?
你这是怎么了？
It's nothing.
没什么
It's not "nothing".
哪里是没什么  怎么了？出了什么事？
Kakeru-kun...
驱君  去公园吧
No.
算了
Then, let's read a book in your room.
那就在房间里读书吧
Yuka-chan...
结花…
You should eat.
吃点东西比较好哦
Go on, take it.
来  吃点
Here.
吵死了
Aww, you spilled it all over.
哎呀  摔扁了
Let me get you some more.
我再去要点
Kakeru-kun...
驱君…
I'm here with you.
有结花陪你呢  有结花陪你呢
I'll always be with you.
我会一直陪着你的
Everything will be all right.
所以没事的
Yuka...
结花
So, you're awake.
回过神来了吗？
Misuzu-senpai...
美铃前辈…我…
You should thank Yuka.
你该感谢结花
When you aimed Raikiri at your throat,
在你把雷切顶到脖子前的时候
Yuka made it disappear by using her power.
结花用能力将雷切消灭  你才得救了
Yuka...
结花她…
Liselotte lost her power too,
莉泽萝忒也失去了战斗能力
though it was only for a moment.
当然只是暂时性的
At that instant, Shiori then brought us to this place.
栞趁机把我们转移到了这里
Is she all right?
她没事吧？
Using her power wore her down,
应该是使用能力而疲劳  还有受到刺激了吧
Kakeru, attempting to take your own life
驱  竟然想自尽  你真是个大笨蛋
"And then the two of them lived happily ever after."
「从那以后两个人便在一起  过上了幸福的生活」
I thought I understood everything, but in reality, I didn't.
我以为自己明白了  却是一无所知
I was a fool.
我真是笨蛋
Kakeru...
驱…
I won't do that again.
我不能消失  不管发生什么事都不能离开结花
As long as I'm alive,
只要我的命还在  我要偿还结花所给我的一切
Thank you, and sorry.
伴随我的感谢
That's why I have to defeat Liselotte!
为此我要打倒莉泽萝忒
For the sake of my friends and for the future.
为了朋友和明日
"As long as I'm alive", is it?
只要命还在…吗
Shiori-san...
栞
Kukuri?
菊理…为什么？
Weren't you an illusion created by Yuka?
不是结花造出来的幻影吗？
She's not the Kukuri-san who existed in Yuka-san's world.
这个人不是在结花的世界里的菊理
I am Abraxas.
我是阿布拉库萨斯
She used to live inside your sister.
是寄宿在驱的姐姐身上的精灵
There was a spirit living inside my sister?
姐姐身上的精灵？
Why?
为什么？
In order to take revenge.
是为了报仇
My master, Satsuki Kukuri,
我的主人菊理自杀了
She thought she could foil Liselotte's plan if there were one less fragment.
因为她认为虚无的碎片只要少一个
Kakeru's sister knew about the Pitfall?
驱的姐姐知道地狱之坠吗？
Yes, she did.
知道  所以我的主人才会杀掉劫之眼的主人  她的弟弟驱
and then end her own life.
而自己也自杀了
Killed...
杀了…我？
Yes.
是的
What does that mean?
怎么回事？驱可是还活着的
I killed you.
我曾经杀了你
I'm sorry, Kakeru.
对不起  驱
Abraxas killed Kakeru-san.
阿布拉库萨斯曾经杀了驱
However, that wasn't the Kakeru-san who carried the Eye of Aion.
但是那并不是拥有劫之眼的驱
The Kakeru-san, who is the vessel of the Eye of Aion,
拥有劫之眼的驱不是在菊理的世界里  而是在其他世界
Yuka's world?
结花的世界吗？
That's correct.
正是  所以你才活着
The Kukuri-san living in Yuka-san's world didn't have a fragment.
结花的世界里的菊理并没有「碎片」
Therefore, she didn't have Abraxas with her.
也没有阿布拉库萨斯  所以才只有她一个死了
Wait a sec.
等等
I don't understand.
我完全搞不懂…
In other words,
也就是说  两个不同世界里的菊理都知晓了同一个事实
and then committed to do the same thing.
采取了一样的行动
The Kukuri-san, who had the fragment, used the spirit Abraxas and killed Kakeru-kun.
拥有「碎片」的那个用精灵阿布拉库萨斯把驱杀了
However, the Kukuri-san in Yuka's world didn't have the spirit, so she couldn't kill Kakeru-kun herself.
但是结花的世界里的菊理并没有精灵
That Kakeru is you.
这个驱就是你  你才是劫之眼的主人
I believe that you originally belonged to the Kukuri-san who carried the fragment.
本来你应该是和拥有「碎片」的菊理一起的
However, at some stage, Yuka-san used her power to drag you into her world,
但是不知在什么阶段  结花用「碎片」的力量把你召唤过去了
subconsciously.
在无意之间
Who told Kukuri-san the truth?
是谁告诉菊理的
I did.
是我
Not just to those two,
不止是两个  在除了赤夜之外的六个世界中
Because I didn't know which Kukuri-san possessed the fragment.
因为不能特定在哪个世界里的菊理是「碎片」的主人
You can travel through space and time?
你能跨越时空吗？
Yes.
是
Why did you tell only Kukuri-san the truth?
为什么你只把事实告诉菊理？
When I received the order, all the other fragments, except Kukuri-san, were quite young.
在我接受指令的那时
So you told my sister to kill herself to protect the world?
你对姐姐说了
I didn't say that.
不是那样的
I merely warned her.
我不过是做了下警告而已
I never expected that things would turn out this way.
只是没想到  结局会是那样…
Calm down, Kakeru.
冷静  驱
I know that my apology won't suffice for the mistake that I made.
我一直都感到非常内疚
I shouldn't have gotten you involved.
要是从来都没有扯上过关系就好了
Perhaps that would have been better.
现在  我是这么想的
The clock is...
这钟…
Yuka!
结花！
The rooftop...
在天台
This isn't the Red Night.
不是赤夜
The master of this world is here.
这个世界的主人在这儿
Yuka!
结花！！
Yuka-san's power has been sealed.
这是把结花的力量给封印住了呢
Satsuki Kakeru, it looks like you no longer wish to kill yourself.
臯月驱
That's good.
如此就好
Give Yuka back!
把结花还来
Then come here.
那样的话  你就过来
Well?
来呀
Kakeru...
驱
Aren't you obedient?
真老实呢
Give Yuka back!
请你把结花还回来
Kakeru-kun...
驱…  君…
The black moon is...
黑月正在…
Well then, let us go to Hell together.
来  一起坠入地狱吧
Kakeru!
驱…
Have some faith in the Black Knights.
应该相信黑骑士们的转变
All right.
好的
Don't get in my way!
别来碍事
Curse you!
可恶…
You bastard!
你这混账
Kakeru-kun!
驱君！
Kakeru!
驱
Are you okay?
你没事吧
Use... my fragment...
请把我的…  碎片…
A doll?
人偶？
She wasn't human?
原来她不是人类？
No, she was.
不  是人
Everything, except her heart and soul, was artificially made.
不过除了心以外  都是人造的
Take the fragment...
这是碎片
Take Shiori-san's fragment.
栞的…
She sacrificed herself to give you this.
以生命为代价的礼物
By using this, you may be successful in sealing her.
如果有这个的话  说不定封印还能够完成
Shiori could travel through space and time.
栞她拥有穿越时空的能力
By using this, along with the power of the Eye of Aion,
要是在这能力的基础上  再加以劫之眼的力量的话…
you can force Liselotte into the gap between dimensions.
就能够将莉泽萝忒封印在时空的夹缝之中
A chance to win... You just have to try.
值得一试
Why did you save Kakeru?
为什么要救驱？
Didn't you want to kill him?
你不是要杀他么？
The chance for the Black Knights to save the world is now zero.
拯救世界的可能性  已经无限接近于零
That's why I thought it'd be interesting to try something new.
既然如此  相信一次  也未尝不可呢
We have no time to hate each other.
没时间供我们争辩了
With Avaritia-sama's current power, the seal won't last for long.
以阿瓦利提亚大人现在的力量
Your efforts are futile!
别再做无谓的挣扎了
Kakeru-kun...
驱君…
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
我不能保护你  真是抱歉
No, Yuka.
才不是呢  结花
I should be the one protecting you.
要保护别人的  是我
From now on, I'll protect you,
我会保护好结花的
always and forever.
从今往后  直到永远
Kakeru-kun...
驱君…
The door of light which locks the darkness,
深锁总光之门
The power of the seven planets that construct the universe,
七惑七星所召
The power of the second star of Ursa Major,
由自草丘之势
Heed my call.
武曲零零
The power of numerous souls, trapped for a thousand years...
急急如律令
Shinuchi Doujigiri Yasutsuna!
真打  童子切安纲
The life-eating sword, Doujigiri Yasutsuna...
噬命之刀  童子切吗
I'll be your shield, Kakeru.
我会成为驱你的盾牌
I see. So you love him too.
是这样啊  你也对驱…
Humans...
说到底还是人呢
It depends on your heart whether you use it to protect or destroy.
不论是毁灭  还是守护
Here she comes!
来了
Avaritia-sama!
阿瓦利提亚大人！
Now, let's end this.
好啦  就让一切结束吧
This is not the end.
我不允许
What?
什么
This is not the end at all!
我不允许结束
It's just the beginning!
这是起点
It's the dawn of a new era!
一切都才刚刚开始
"Hope" is just a fool's dream that brings despair in the end.
希望  只不过是为了品尝绝望而生的  愚蠢的梦境而已
Quit blabbering!
别自说自话
I've finally understood my mistakes,
明明好不容易才觉察到了自己的错误
and have finally decided to rectify them.
明明好不容易才决定要从此改变自己
Why do you want to erase the future?
可你为什么又要把明天就此抹去？
Kakeru-kun...
驱君…
No matter who says so, I will never give up!
不管谁叫我放手  我都绝不言弃
Even if I'm told that hope ends with despair, I just won't give up!
就算有人说  希望的尽头  只有绝望在等着我
Good things and bad things coexist, and the same thing applies for good guys and bad guys.
世事有好亦有坏
Let's change whatever we have right now if you're not satisfied.
要是如今不如意  亲手改变就是
You lose everything if you just give up, right?
如果放弃了  不就万事皆休了么？
You're just a child.
真是个孩子呢
That's right.
嗯  是啊
To you, it's no more than a kid whining, right?
在你听来  也许这只不过是孩子的戏言
However, I believe it.
可我却真心实意地这么想
I believe in the future!
相信着明天
I thought I was alone.
我曾以为自己是孤身一人
I planned on surviving on my own.
也以为自己是靠着一己之力独活下来的
But I was wrong.
可是  事实却并非如此
I've had people supporting me all this time.
在我身后  一直都有人在支持我
Yuka was always there for me.
有结花在我身边
Yuka was always by my side, so I didn't lose myself.
就是因为有结花在我身边  我才没有迷失自我
All thanks to Yuka...
这都是结花的功劳呀…
Kakeru-kun...
驱君…
The world...
这世界
Yuka and the future,
还有我和结花的未来
I'll protect it all!
都将由我来守护
Keep trying.
要真能守护得住  你就守来看看吧
Liselotte...
莉泽萝忒啊…
Verard...!
维拉德？
He's speaking through the Eye of Aion?
思念  从劫之眼里头…
Stop it.
住手吧
Don't steal their future.
你不能夺走这些人的未来
Verard..
维拉德…
What are you...?
你说什么…？
I was mistaken.
我错了
I couldn't see the hearts of men.
从前  我看不到世人的内心
This boy taught me that.
是这个少年告诉了我这一切
Please understand, Liselotte.
希望你能明白  莉泽萝忒
Don't destroy the world.
不可以抹杀这个世界
Verard...
维拉德…
I have absolutely no doubt left in me anymore!
我已经不会再犹豫了
I waited 800 years to get hold of the shard of the Emerald Tablet,
我苦忍了八百年的孤独  想要的便只有这…
Senpai!
前辈！
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Put all your spirit into it, Misuzu.
快集气  美铃
Child... oh child...
童子哟童子
Eat away my life, become the demon, release the power of the sun to defeat the vast hatred in the world.
食我血肉
Kigazettou!
消失吧
That won't work on me!
无用的抵抗…
How dare you...!
可恶…
I won't let you.
怎可能让你得逞！
Sleep forever, Witch of Babylon!
永远地睡去吧
Let go of me!
放手！
NOOO!!!!
不要！！！
Avaritia-sama...
阿瓦利提亚大人…
What's happening?
什么？
Now that its master is no more, the Red Night is collapsing.
失去了主人的赤夜  已经开始崩溃了
It's all right.
没事的
I'll take you back.
我送你们回去
I didn't expect that a future like this was even possible.
也有这样的未来呢
Misuzu, take care of the Kusakabe clan.
美铃
I will.
是
Thank you.
谢谢…
Yuka...
结花？
Ohh, Kakeru, you're trying to be alone with Yuka again, aren't you?
哎呀  驱君你啊  又跟结花来孤男寡女啦？
You can't, you can't!
这可不行  不行的哦
I want to get lovey-dovey as well!
也让人家也甜蜜蜜  疯颠颠嘛
Don't utter words which you don't even understand!
别说些神经兮兮的话
Idiot!
笨蛋
Since that day, Yuka and I never spoke about the Red Night again.
从那以后  我和结花  都没有再提过赤夜的事
Did you know that if you open the big doll, a little doll comes out from inside?
然后呢
And then, if you open that doll, another little one comes out!
然后再打开那小不倒翁一看
Takahisa!
贤久！
You took money from my wallet again, didn't you?!
又擅自从我钱包里顺手牵羊
Oh damn...
不好
Takahisa-senpai, I didn't get to the main part yet...
啊  贤久前辈
You're gotta pay for it, Takahisa!
你得用身体来还债  贤久
But it's just 150 yen!
不就150日元嘛
But it's my 150 yen! Wait right there!!
150日元还嫌少  你给我站住…
Yukiko and Takahisa don't know us.
雪子和贤久也不知道我们的故事
Kukuri-neesan and Shiori-san aren't here either.
这里  既没有菊理姐  也没有栞
Hey!
好啊
Misuzu-senpai...
美铃前辈
I'm about to go to Ayanasu, wanna come?
我想去阿亚纳斯逛逛  要是方便的话  能不能陪我一起呢
Yeah.
没问题
Whose world is this? I don't know.
我不知道这是谁的世界
However, I find it peaceful here.
但是  在这里  却有一份安乐与平静
The weather's good, right?
天气不错呢
Huh?
嗯
Ah, yeah, it's good.
嗯  真不错呢
There was no future in that world,
如果那不是未来的话
but this world will definitely have a future.
那这个世界  便还会拥有明天
Will I see you tomorrow?
明天 会到来吗？